Doc ID1200083
99.8% Similarity
Conference Bike
The bike has a circular jointed drive-shaft and rack & pinion steering. Conference Bike
 
 The ConferenceBike is a 7-seat human powered vehicle created by artist Eric Staller and manufactured in The Netherlands.


Doc ID1017636
99.8% Similarity
Del Mar station
As of 2015, the bike room has not been well-maintained, however, and many of the racks are damaged or broken. This station has a parking lot with 290 reserved paid parking spaces and an open bike room with 26 bike spaces.


Doc ID249504
99.8% Similarity
Noosa Heads  Queensland
Bike racks are provided in all shopping and beach precincts. There are dedicated bike lanes throughout the shire.


Doc ID1019144
99.1% Similarity
Panhandle Trail
There are stations and special areas that serve as access points and provide parking places and also features like permanent restrooms, portable restrooms, shelter houses, picnic tables, vending machines, water fountains, maps, bike racks, and bulletin boards that provide event notifications and maps. This makes the trail suitable for walking, running, biking, horseback riding, and cross country skiing; however, motorized vehicles are prohibited.


Doc ID1023804
99.1% Similarity
Lafarge LakeûDouglas station
The station features 4 bus passenger pickup/drop-off bays along Pinetree Way, a dedicated HandyDART area, night bus service, bike lockers/racks, and 150 City of Coquitlam-managed "Park and Ride" parking spaces. Nearby amenities include the BMX bike park, City Centre Aquatic Complex, Coquitlam City Hall, Coquitlam RCMP and Fire Department, Coquitlam Town Centre, Douglas College (David Lam campus), Evergreen Cultural Centre, Lafarge Lake, Percy Perry Stadium, Pinetree Secondary School, Town Centre Park, and Tri-Cities Chamber of Commerce.


0:02:32.987982
