Doc ID972422
81.6% Similarity
F29 Retaliator
The game was developed during the end of the Cold War, based mostly on speculations on then-future aircraft that were expected to be in use by the year 2002, in particular based on the design of the Lockheed Martin F-22 and the Grumman X-29A. "Computer Gaming World" described "F29" as a less-expensive alternative which "still offers a solid game-playing experience, with limitations".


Doc ID628558
81.6% Similarity
Christopher Rowley
Rowley's first science fiction novel was "The War for Eternity", published in 1983, that won him the Compton Crook Award for best first novel. "The War for Eternity" led to three further novels set in the same future: "The Black Ship", "The Founder" and "To a Highland Nation".


Doc ID581934
81.6% Similarity
120 mm M1 gun
The M1 gun entered service late in World War II. After World War II ended and the Cold War with the Soviet Union began, M1 guns were deployed in many locations in the U.S. and Canada.


Doc ID992649
81.6% Similarity
Shadow Squadron
The player controls one of two star fighters; like "Star Wars Arcade" and "Star Fox", the ships are built with polygons. If the player chooses the second fighter they will have the option of choosing auto-pilot, which allows the computer to fly and the player to concentrate on fighting.


Doc ID665001
81.6% Similarity
Above and Beyond  miniseries 
The miniseries deals with the Atlantic Ferry Organization, tasked with ferrying aircraft from North America to Europe in the early years of the Second World War. In 1940, Canadian weapons of war, including newly manufactured aircraft ordered by the British, have to be delivered to the United Kingdom.


0:03:10.520545
