Doc ID1
100.0% Similarity
MoroccoûSaudi Arabia relations
During the current Yemeni Civil War, Morocco participates as part of the anti-Houthi coalition led by Saudi Arabia, with 6 planes and 1,500 troops. MoroccoûSaudi Arabia relations
 
 MoroccanûSaudi Arabian relations refers to the current and historical relations between Morocco and Saudi Arabia.


Doc ID791704
100.0% Similarity
Order of Battle January 28 Incident
This was a brief war between the armies of the Republic of China and the Empire of Japan that occurred prior to the Second Sino-Japanese War. Order of Battle January 28 Incident
 
 This is an Order of Battle for January 28 Incident.


Doc ID792013
100.0% Similarity
To Die in Italbar
To escape his fate, "H" must go with Sandow and others to the devastated remains of the Earth, destroyed in a recent war, where Sandow engages in a duel of powers to drive out the goddess. To Die in Italbar
 
 To Die in Italbar (1973) is a science fiction novel by American writer Roger Zelazny.


Doc ID792010
100.0% Similarity
Kiyonao Ichiki
He ordered an immediate attack on Wanping, precipitating the first real battle of the Second Sino-Japanese War. With the start of the Pacific War in 1941, Ichiki was promoted to colonel and was placed in command of the IJA 28th Infantry Regiment, from the 7th Division, which consisted of 3,000 troops, and was assigned to assault and occupy Midway island.


Doc ID792004
100.0% Similarity
9th Brigade  Australia 
The 9th Brigade was originally formed as part of the First Australian Imperial Force for service during the First World War. This was followed by the Second Battle of Morlancourt before the battalion took part in the final offensive of the war, the Hundred Days Offensive.


0:01:50.632263
