Doc ID280352
100.0% Similarity
Bat World Sanctuary
Bat World Sanctuary
 
 Bat World Sanctuary was founded in 1994 as a non-profit rescue-rehabilitation center and sanctuary operated exclusively for bats. Bat World Sanctuary is accredited with both the Global Federation of Animal Sanctuaries.


Doc ID536429
100.0% Similarity
World Scout Indaba
Prince Henry, Duke of Gloucester, as president of the British Scout Association, brought the Indaba to a close with these words: "Let it be the determination of all who have been here at Gilwell to spread the Scout spirit wherever they go, that spirit of peace and friendliness which is so sorely needed in the world today". World Scout Indaba
 
 The World Scout Indaba was a gathering of Scout Leaders from around the world.


Doc ID486525
100.0% Similarity
Pax World Funds
Pax World integrates Environmental Social and Corporate Governance (ESG) factors into investment analysis and portfolio construction. Their vehicle, the first broadly diversified, publicly available mutual fund to use social as well as financial criteria in the investment decision-making process, was the Pax World Fund, predecessor of what is now the Pax World Balanced Fund.


Doc ID767972
100.0% Similarity
Ancient Future  group 
jpg
 
 Formed in late 1978 by Matthew Montfort, Ancient Future coined the term "world fusion music" to describe its use of Indian, African, Balinese, Middle Eastern, and South American rhythms, the rich harmonies of Europe, the peaceful melodies of Asia, and other musical traditions within a contemporary framework. They use their knowledge of world music to create something new and uniquely their own that is respected by pundits from other cultures whose traditions are a part of the mix.


Doc ID805273
100.0% Similarity
Boy Scouts of the United Nations
In a full-page cartoon from the July 1929 Punch magazine, entitled "Patrols of Peace", the League of Nations, represented as a goddess, looks out at the 3rd World Scout Jamboree, held in Birkenhead, Merseyside, England, saying, "They say I've got no army; but why should I want one with these allies"? The World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts and the World Organization of the Scout Movement have formal consultative relations with UNESCO.


0:02:34.612249
